<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Street Photography Gallery on Runfeng Yang</title>
    <link>/photos/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Street Photography Gallery on Runfeng Yang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2023 Runfeng Yang
</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/photos/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2022-2023@Padova</title>
      <link>/photos/2022-2023-padova/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/photos/2022-2023-padova/</guid>
      <description>Heart-shaped Cloud Took at the department of Statistic of university of Pavoda. Cyberpunk 2022 People are having fun at a local festival in Padova. Color of Dusk Some collections of dusk sence. The first one is took at the Monselice. Others were taken in Pavoda. New Year Wizard! A Peek of Autumn In autumn colors are so mixed. Lago di Garda Snow and Mountain! Shooting Took at the market of Verona </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021@Madrid</title>
      <link>/photos/2021-madrid/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/photos/2021-madrid/</guid>
      <description>Mom&amp;amp;Child Metro in the Snow 2021.01 Madrid had its biggest snow in 50 years Sunset in the Lake Took the photo when I was having a walk in the lake of Casa de Campo Encounter At the central street of Alcala, two dogs met each other Christmas Belongs to Childern 2021, Christmas in Madrid. It seems that only children are really having fun with this festival Pondered Woman Royal Peacock Who is the real king/queen here in the palace?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2022@Madrid</title>
      <link>/photos/2022-madrid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/photos/2022-madrid/</guid>
      <description>The Moon Took in January when the night sky was crystal clear. Spring in Madrid Madrid is full of flowers when in Spring. This year we didn&amp;rsquo;t have snows City Hidden in Flowers Kids and Dogs They are so energetic that reminds me of the days when I was young. </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
